We're getting ready to assemble our button mirror now.
I just want to let you know these things come in all different sizes and shapes, from one inch all the way up to six inch.
Also I want to mention, when I cut this, this is tempered glass, and if you want to get a good smooth cut, always cut on tempered glass.
It won't dull your blade.
If you noticed, this is just a razorblade and it won't dull the razorblade.
If you cut on regular glass, it's going to dull your blade really quick and will ruin it fast.
So now, we're getting ready to put this into our device, in our button press.
First thing we need, this is called a shell, and we'll put it in, assemble here.
With this, you can make buttons, mirrors.
This is a little magnet you can stick on here.
So you can make them into a lot of different things once you get going.
But mirrors, I found that most people like them the best.
So now we're going to put it in here, assemble it up.
First we put in our hologram paper, then we put in our newly designed and colored transparency.
Now we put a piece of miter over on it.
This holds it together and keeps it from falling apart once it goes into the press and then we just press it down.
That's stage one.